Compiles an Angular app into an output directory named dist/ at the given output path. Must be executed from within a workspace directory.
usage: ng build <project> [options]

arguments:
  project
    The name of the project to build. Can be an application or a library.

options:
  --allowed-common-js-dependencies 
    A list of CommonJS packages that are allowed to be used without a build time warning.
  --aot 
    Build using Ahead of Time compilation.
  --base-href 
    Base url for the application being built.
  --build-event-log 
    **EXPERIMENTAL** Output file path for Build Event Protocol events
  --build-optimizer 
    Enables '@angular-devkit/build-optimizer' optimizations when using the 'aot' option.
  --common-chunk 
    Use a separate bundle containing code used across multiple bundles.
  --configuration (-c)
    A named build target, as specified in the "configurations" section of angular.json.
    Each named target is accompanied by a configuration of option defaults for that target.
    Setting this explicitly overrides the "--prod" flag
  --cross-origin 
    Define the crossorigin attribute setting of elements that provide CORS support.
  --delete-output-path 
    Delete the output path before building.
  --deploy-url 
    URL where files will be deployed.
  --experimental-rollup-pass 
    Concatenate modules with Rollup before bundling them with Webpack.
  --extract-css 
    Extract CSS from global styles into '.css' files instead of '.js'.
  --extract-licenses 
    Extract all licenses in a separate file.
  --fork-type-checker 
    Run the TypeScript type checker in a forked process.
  --help 
    Shows a help message for this command in the console.
  --i18n-file 
    Localization file to use for i18n.
  --i18n-format 
    Format of the localization file specified with --i18n-file.
  --i18n-locale 
    Locale to use for i18n.
  --i18n-missing-translation 
    How to handle missing translations for i18n.
  --index 
    Configures the generation of the application's HTML index.
  --lazy-modules 
    List of additional NgModule files that will be lazy loaded. Lazy router modules will be discovered automatically.
  --localize 
    Translate the bundles in one or more locales.
  --main 
    The full path for the main entry point to the app, relative to the current workspace.
  --named-chunks 
    Use file name for lazy loaded chunks.
  --ngsw-config-path 
    Path to ngsw-config.json.
  --optimization 
    Enables optimization of the build output. Including minification of scripts and styles, tree-shaking, dead-code elimination and fonts inlining. For more information, see https://angular.io/guide/workspace-config#optimization-and-source-map-configuration.
  --output-hashing 
    Define the output filename cache-busting hashing mode.
  --output-path 
    The full path for the new output directory, relative to the current workspace.
    
    By default, writes output to a folder named dist/ in the current project.
  --poll 
    Enable and define the file watching poll time period in milliseconds.
  --polyfills 
    The full path for the polyfills file, relative to the current workspace.
  --preserve-symlinks 
    Do not use the real path when resolving modules. If unset then will default to `true` if NodeJS option --preserve-symlinks is set.
  --prod 
    Shorthand for "--configuration=production".
    When true, sets the build configuration to the production target.
    By default, the production target is set up in the workspace configuration such that all builds make use of bundling, limited tree-shaking, and also limited dead code elimination.
  --progress 
    Log progress to the console while building.
  --resources-output-path 
    The path where style resources will be placed, relative to outputPath.
  --service-worker 
    Generates a service worker config for production builds.
  --show-circular-dependencies 
    Show circular dependency warnings on builds.
  --source-map 
    Output source maps.
  --stats-json 
    Generates a 'stats.json' file which can be analyzed using tools such as 'webpack-bundle-analyzer'.
  --subresource-integrity 
    Enables the use of subresource integrity validation.
  --ts-config 
    The full path for the TypeScript configuration file, relative to the current workspace.
  --vendor-chunk 
    Use a separate bundle containing only vendor libraries.
  --verbose 
    Adds more details to output logging.
  --watch 
    Run build when files change.
  --web-worker-ts-config 
    TypeScript configuration for Web Worker modules.
